<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>HydroHamed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HydroHamed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 18 Jul 2024 12:24:29 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Hydroinformatics?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/hydroinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/hydroinformatics/</guid>
      <description>This article delves into the multifaceted world of hydroinformatics, exploring its history, applications, job market, and future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hydroinformatics Engineer Roadmap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/hydroinformatics-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/hydroinformatics-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>This roadmap outlines the essential study topics and skills needed to work as a hydroinformatics engineer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Let&#39;s Connect</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! Whether you have a question, a project idea, or just want to chat about the fascinating world of hydroinformatics, I&amp;rsquo;m all ears.
Reach Me Here 📧 Email: hydrohamed@gmail.com
💼 Connect with me on LinkedIn
🐙 Check out my GitHub
✖️ Follow me on X</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my projects page! Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find some of the projects I&amp;rsquo;ve built and contributed to. They blend my passion for water, coding, and open-source development.
eOceans Mobile App Empowering Citizen Scientists and Researchers to Study Oceans
I contributed to the development of the eOceans mobile app, a powerful tool for citizen scientists, researchers, and teams exploring and studying the world&amp;rsquo;s oceans. This app enables users to capture valuable data about ocean environments in real-time, contributing to faster and more collaborative discoveries.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Story</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>I&amp;rsquo;m Hamed Samsami, a Hydroinformatics Engineer from Iran, now living in beautiful Norway. My story is about merging two passions: water and technology.
Teenage Coder: The Early Days As a teenager, I spent countless late nights at my computer. While my friends were playing video games and chatting on Yahoo, I was learning to write code and participating in programming competitions.
My interest in computer science never waned. Even while studying civil engineering, I used my free time to build websites for friends, local schools, and various small projects.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
