<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom" xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/">
  <channel>
    <title>HydroHamed</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/</link>
    <description>Recent content on HydroHamed</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- 0.128.2</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 16 Jul 2024 02:19:08 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Hydroinformatics? Bridging Water Science and Technology</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/hydroinformatics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 13 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/hydroinformatics/</guid>
      <description>This article delves into the multifaceted world of hydroinformatics, exploring its history, applications, job market, and future prospects.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Hydroinformatics Engineer Roadmap</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/articles/hydroinformatics-roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 15 Jul 2024 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/articles/hydroinformatics-roadmap/</guid>
      <description>This roadmap outlines the essential study topics and skills needed to work as a hydroinformatics engineer.</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Get in Touch</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/contact/</guid>
      <description>Hello there! Whether you have a question, a project idea, or just want to chat about the fascinating world of hydroinformatics, I&amp;rsquo;m all ears.
Reach Me Here Feel free to drop me a message using any of the contact methods below. I promise to get back to you as soon as I can.
Email: 📧 hydrohamed@gmail.com
LinkedIn: 💼 Connect with me on LinkedIn
Visit My Digital Garden Curious about what I&amp;rsquo;m currently working on?</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Projects</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/projects/</guid>
      <description>Welcome to my projects page! Here you&amp;rsquo;ll find different projects I&amp;rsquo;ve worked on. They mix my love for water science, computer programming, and free software.
HydroHamed A Hub for Hydroinformatics Enthusiasts
HydroHamed is my online space for sharing knowledge about water science and technology. It&amp;rsquo;s for engineers, researchers, scientists, and anyone interested in this field. You can find helpful information, guides, and discussions here.
🔗 Explore HydroHamed
Flood Events Database A Citizen Science Project for Gathering Flood Events Data</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>My Story</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/about/</guid>
      <description>Water has always been a big part of my life, but it was computer programming that truly set me on my path. I&amp;rsquo;m Hamed Samsami, a Hydroinformatics Engineer from Iran, now living in beautiful Norway. My story is all about merging two passions: water and technology.
How It All Started As a teenager, I spent countless late nights at my computer. While my friends were playing video games and chatting on Yahoo, I was learning to write code.</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
